itempad.com 2008-12-18

# itempad article site publishing community

## Itempad.com Privacy Policy

At itempad.com we offer visitors the advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. 

We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We will never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party. Period. How we gather information from users 

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters in forums, and other interactive areas of our site. 

Like most Web sites, Itempad.com also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit. 

What we do with the information we collect Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone. 

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on www. itempad.com to communicate with you about your registration and customisation preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by www. itempad.com and other topics we think you might find of interest. Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements 

itempad.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. Contacting Us We can be reached by emailing us.
